http://www.bigbend.edu/privacy-policy

Getting Started
DREAMers!
Campus Map
DREAMers!
Tutorials for Online Classes
Transitional Studies (Open Doors/HS21/GED/ABE/ESL)
Library
STEM Center (Tutoring)
ON CAMPUS
Report-It!
Campus Tours & Outreach
Community & Professional Education (CBIS)
Quick Links
Advanced Technologies Education Center (ATEC)
Privacy Policy
Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.
Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.
We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.
We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.
We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.
Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.
We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.
We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.
Privacy Policy
Something extraordinary is happening at Big Bend Community CollegeBBCC nursing students achieved a 100-percent pass rate on their first attempt at the national NCLEX board exam for registered nurses in 11 of the last 12 years. The school was voted the third-best nursing program in the State of Washington by the website registerednursing.org..
Popular Searches
BBCC Academic Calendar
Canvas
Class Schedule
Financial Aid
Annual Security Report
Press ReleasesBoeing donates $50,000 to Big Bend aviation programsBBCC TRIO Programs celebrate National First-Generation DayBig Bend’s Garoutte selected to sit on NFCA BoardPhi Theta Kappa inducts 17 new members NewsBig Bend nursing students excel through difficultiesTerry Leas reflects on higher education careerBig Bend Celebrates TRiO Upward Bound Program With Drive Thru ParadeMicrosoft donates $10K for Big Bend Computer Science program scholarships
Athletic NewsVikings sweep Miles City, Ray picks up two winsVikings split 4-game weekend series at home with Pierce CollegeVikings softball picks up three wins at crossover tournamentBig Bend Baseball splits weekend series with Centralia, 2-2
Home | Admissions | Academics | Student Life | Information | Contact | SitemapAccessibility | Non-Discrimination Policy | Privacy Policy | Publication Disclaimer | Support | Terms of Use7662 Chanute Street N.E. • Moses Lake, WA 98837 • 509-793-2222 • 877-745-1212 • TDD 509-793-2325
© Copyright 2013 Big Bend Community College
Covid-19 InformationRead More
+
